Hello, welcome to the tree episode of Learn German in Hindi.
In the last episode, we took a test on German basis.
In this episode, the most
important thing for me is Modal Bhaar and along with that, we will
take future tense and questions request petitions. Next week, the exam
which is going to be held is also
important. The SSP of that country is going to
take the test. So, I will request you to
revise in the next 7 days if possible. Sure, you will be
prepared for it. Okay, let's start
today's test. Right now, you will see 25 questions on the screen.
As I said last time,
solve the question immediately
and pause here. Try to solve it without any help.
And when you have solved it, take the
pause and we can move ahead.
I hope that all of you must have asked
25 questions. Now we will see the answers.
Put it in Google a little quick revision.
What happens in the mode of class? Why are there
London etc.  What happens in it is the
mode square is in the second position it moves
and male worker and mix in female goes
for example I can do it is the victim
pizza action happened selected pizza
person union pizza Edison juice let's
see the answer so let's
start immediately icon play cricket this scandal
cricket clearance filler will not work you
must speak the word you should learn
German schedule watch Lebanon 122 happens then if you do
n't put it then you make a lot of
mistakes yasmin muslims of
women in leave it gym we will
see when we see how for now these are also ok that can meet Anil
Aaron Anil fun humor drink coffee
milk a patriarch that good night to learn
Spanish would like to what all is
newston that's why admit Spanish layer not I have to
play tennis this trick question have to
mean this ancestral speed learn she
can visit Paris teeth Paris Baiju Khan now
we go into that I will
lead leaf ishq veritor pass
pencil welding  At the end of this we will
check the German, let's do this success also,
he will do it for ourselves, okay next you will meet
Andheri door beans Anil Saif, he will play
football with such pass screen will learn English well done English lu
and on Thursday we
see the question and where is Anil, he is Anil do do do it is the question
again how many how many cars will
come together that is why those wheeler auto
ships are 20, if you want to respect then
drink this no question Prince break then
play cricket speed cricket's European
Jaisan Mian this cricket pitch cricket pillar
and favorite request you to give one I
hope that all of you must have done that,
whatever is written below from the market, if you do
not understand anything then do that device as
I said in the next we are going to subscribe,
we will meet in this episode
next, thank you